Uru-chan, thank you for your hard work.
う るちゃん、お疲れ
Ah, manager, thank you for your hard work.
あ、店長、お疲れ様です
I want to hire someone, but what are you doing tomorrow?
人入れたいんだけど、明日って何やってる?
I have university tomorrow, so I can't go in.
明日、大学があるんで、入れないんですよね
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなんですか
Sorry.
ごめんね
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
Nami-chan.
なみちゃん
picture?
え?
Mr. Ushikawa?
牛川さん?
It's a coincidence.
偶然だね
偶然ですね
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
Can I send you something?
何か送れますか?
Recently, a friend of mine had a birthday coming up, so I sent her a present.
最近、友達が誕生日近くて、 それでプレゼントを送りました
Last time, eh?
前回、 え?
Did you see it?
見てたんですか?
Why were you writing me a message?
なんで僕にメッセージ書いてたんですか?
Sorry.
すいません
Did you write a message?
メッセージ書いてたんですか?
Who were you writing to?
誰に書いてたんですか?
I wonder what you were watching.
あなた、 何 で 見てたんだろうね
You gated it with gloves.
手袋でさ、ゲートしてたでしょ
Did you see it?
見てたんですか?
Are you going to write that to this guy?
それ、こいつに書くの?
No, it's not.
いや、違います
Take it off.
脱ぎよ
Nami-chan, she takes off her clothes because of her skin.
なみちゃんってさ、 肌もそうで脱ぐんだよね
No.
違います
Take it off.
脱ぎよ
Let's get excited.
バテで行こう
Sorry, sorry.
すいません、すいません
pa
パ
Hey hey,
ンツ ねえねえじゃん、
that.
それ
My feet turned into insects.
足、 そこで虫になって
Hold the bug and use your legs as hard as you can.
虫を持たれかかって、 足を思いっきりやり
Walk your feet too.
足も歩いて
Try sitting on Kurt yourself.
自分で、クルトに座ってみて
When did this come off?
いつ脱げたの、これは
Are you taking it off?
脱げてんの?
This is coming off.
脱げてるじゃん、これ
This feels like it's coming off now.
これ、今脱げてる感じじゃん
I can't see it.
見えてない
Could you please open it a little?
ちょっと開いてみせてくれない?
Show it to grandpa, forever.
おじいちゃんに見せてよ、ずっと
It's wet.
濡 れてんじゃん
You're wet, Nami-chan.
濡れてるよ、なみちゃん
Speak out, voice.
声出して、声
Speak out loud.
声出して
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫か?
Open it yourself.
開いて、自分で
It's Kurt, but let's take him out.
クルトですが、抜き出しになるように
happy?
嬉しい?
Are you happy?
嬉しいでしょ?
Won't you tell me that you're happy?
嬉しいですって言ってくんない?
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
Look at me.
こっち見てって
My legs are covered in sleep.
足が寝間ついてるじゃん
I went to bed.
寝間ついてちゃったよ
If you look closely, you'll see that it's Brasuketen.
よく見たらさ、 ブラスケてんじゃん、
this.
これ
Ami-chan, but she was punished.
あみちゃん、でも処分だったんだ
Do you have sex during gymnastics?
体操でもセックスするの?
Yeah.
うん
You're stuck.
手止まってんじゃん
Reach out your hand.
手を伸ばして
If I could go, I would have to have sex with him.
行けるというのは彼とはセックスしたらか
Keep your voice out.
声抜いて
Chan
ちゃん
And, hey, speak louder.
と、 ほら、もっと声をして
Let's feel it.
感じてみしょ
Are you happy?
嬉しいでしょ?
You're happy to be touched, aren't you?
目を触られて嬉しいでしょ?
Hey, you're always happy, aren't you?
ちょっと、お前嬉しいでしょ、いつも
happy?
嬉しい?
Are you asking me if I'm happy?
嬉しいかって聞いてんの?
Who said it without permission?
誰が勝手に言って言っちゃった?
I didn't say it all at once.
一気に言ってない
Right?
よね?
Ah, it's falling.
あー、 落ちる
How far can I fall?
落ちんどこまで、これだけ?
Isn't it like this?
こうでしょ?
Look.
ほら
Does the falling place move?
落ちんどこって動くの?
Yeah.
うん
Cut one out, this one.
一つ切り出して、こっち
Look, what happened?
ほら、何があったんや?
Move it.
動かせ
Look at me, what kind of face do you have?
どんな顔してるんだ、こっち見て
This is how I saw it
こう見してきたんだ
Yo.
よ
Isn't it okay to use it?
使 えていいんじゃない?
Make yourself feel good, here.
ちゃんと気持ちよくして、こっちを
What did you say?
何かって言ってんだよ
I can say it.
言えんだよ
Head this way.
こっち向けよ
Just do this for a moment.
ちょっと、ここをしてろ
Do this.
ここをしてろ
Stop it.
やめろ
I'll think about this.
ここを考えとってやるよ
Does this feel good?
これ、気持ちいいの?
Isn't it like this?
こうでしょ?
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
Don't go.
行くじゃねえよ
Don't just go there.
勝手に行くんじゃねえよ
Let's go, okay.
行けよ、ちゃんと
Don't go because you're going on your own.
勝手に行くから、行くんじゃねえよ
Go.
行け
Cry.
泣きしろ
Why are you crying?
なんで泣いてるんだよ
Looks like they're raping me.
こっちレープしてるみたいだよ
Why are you crying?
なんで泣いてるんだよ
なんで泣いてるんだ?
Are you happy?
嬉しいの?
嬉しいんでしょ?
Are you happy?
嬉しいの?
Ayumi-chan, have you really started to like me?
あゆみちゃん、大分僕のこと好きになった?
You fell in love with it, right?
好きになったでしょ?
Can you please look at me?
こっち見てってくんない?
Didn't the previous ones work?
前の彼らはつかなかった?
I'll make you feel good, so watch me.
気持ちよくしてあげるから、見てて
hey.
ね
Hey, look at me carefully.
ほ ら、ちゃんとこっち見てね
No way.
だめじゃん
Look at me.
こっち見ててよ
見てて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
You have a great voice.
すごい声出てるじゃん
I'm crying.
泣いてる
I'll tell you exactly when I go.
行 くときは言うんだよ、ちゃんと
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い
Is once an end?
一回とは終わり?
Which one?
どっち?
I can't go again and again.
何回でも行けない
Can I go as many times as I want?
何回でも行けんの?
How many times do you want to go?
何回でも行きたいの?
I'll get someone to come.
誰で来てもらってあげるよ
Look.
ほ ら
That's interesting.
おもしろいね
Your butt is twitching.
お尻がピクピクしてるじゃん
Take it easy.
ゆっくりして
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Do it while opening your butt.
お尻を開けながらやって
Open your ass and come here.
ケツ開けて、こっちに
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Just look for Retch.
レッチだけ探してね
Look over here.
こ っち向いて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Tell me you love me.
好 きって言って
Say it as much as you want.
い っぱい言って
like.
好き
Let's get it out.
出そう
I'll put it out.
出すよ